[Music]
[Música]
Okay, let's start watching some
bueno eh vamos a empezar a ver un
gossip that I left behind from the other
chismecito que me dejé atrás del otro
day that we didn't have time to discuss. What
día que no nos dio tiempo a tratar Cuál
was the last live show we did? The
fue el último directo que hicimos la
truth is that the gossip is pretty
verdad es que está el salseo bastante
calm, they're not giving us much crap, they're not
tranqui no nos están dando mucha trua no
giving us much of a break, eh. But
nos están dando mucha tregua eh Pero
anyway, it's not bad for me because the truth
bueno no me viene mal porque la verdad
is that I'm super busy with the
es que estoy super ocupado con el canal
main channel. Tomorrow we have a live show on
principal mañana tenemos un directazo en
the main channel that doesn't make sense.
el canal principal que no tiene sentido
Tomorrow we have a live show on the
mañana tenemos un directazo en el canal
main channel that doesn't make sense. Okay,
principal que no tiene sentido Bueno
family, friends, let's watch it on Whatever
familia amigos vamos a verlo de Whatever
to see what happened, apparently he cheated on his
a ver qué ha pasado que por lo visto le
girlfriend, I don't
puso la cuerna a la novia salido una no
know, the truth is, let's see it here. The
sé la verdad vamos a verlo aquí el
crime of infamy doesn't exist in
delito de infama no existe en Ciudad de
Mexico City. Fernanda Blas is about to lose
México Fernanda Blas a punto de perder
her social networks, the strong
sus redes sociales las fuertes
confessions she just made. And why do
confesiones que acaba de hacer Y por qué
many fans believe that she's moving the
muchos fanáticos creen que mueve la
viper Javi, but who do we mess
vipero Javi pero con quién nos metemos
with, who do we mess with? Nobody remembers
con quién nos metemos Ya nadie recuerda
delox anymore. Well, look, I was talking on the
delox Pues mira estuve hablando por
phone with him the day before yesterday or around there, he'll come, he'll come, he'll
teléfono con él antesde ayer o por ahí
come here in
en vendrá vendrá vendrá para acá dentro
a few days, it's probably that  We don't
de unos días seguramente es que tampoco
have many topics to talk about either We
tenemos muchos temas de los que hablar
don't have many topics to
tampoco tenemos muchos temas de los que
talk about because I have a feeling that they're going to
hablar por qué presiento que van a
cut this live too no man
cortar este directo también no hombre
neurof funker This no my goodness eh my goodness I do
neurof funker Este no madre mía eh madre
n't know neurofunk if we should address that topic
mía no sé neurofunk si tratar ese tema
on telesalseo in the next live in
en telesalseo en el próximo directo en
tomorrow's live because don't you see what he's
el directo de mañana porque no ver que
messing around The gentleman no you don't see what he
está liando El caballero no no ve a la
's messing around the gentleman doesn't show any
que está lidando el caballero no apunta
signs of showing signs of the next bad
maneras a apunta maneras a a próximo
guy no Werever has a
malito no Werever tiene un video
compromising video about her that he's going to release very
comprometedor sobre ella que lanzará muy
soon let's see what's going on why do you
pronto veamos qué está pasando por qué
think that her family Yes I knew I
piensas que su familia Sí lo sabía yo
never said that in any video I said that well they
nunca dije eso en ningún video dije eso
took that out of context guys
pues eso lo sacaron de contexto chicos
we have an update on this topic
tenemos una actualización con este tema
and that is that Fernanda Blas has been
y es que Fernanda Blas ha estado
doing daily live shows on YouTube
haciendo directo os diarios En YouTube
however she decided to publish this reel
sin embargo decidió publicar este reel
if you go to her profile you can
si ustedes van a su perfil se pueden
see that it already has more than a million
percatar que ya tiene más de un millón
views where if we click on it she
de reproducciones donde si le damos clic
says the following you in the middle of an
dice lo siguiente tú en pleno ataque de
anxiety attack because the narcissist took you
ansiedad porque el narcisista te llevó
to the limit we wait a few seconds and
al límite esperamos unos segundos y
look at this the narcissist recording himself To
miren esto el narcisista grabándose Para
have evidence and say that you're crazy
tener evidencia y decir que estás loca
among the comments of  it's real we have
entre los comentarios de es real tenemos
no words for the indignation and
no hay palabras para la indignación y
hatred that I have for those types of people
Odio que le tengo a ese tipo de personas
old school influencers
los influencers de la vieja escuela
Luisito Werever among others use it for
Luisito Werever entre otros lo usan para
women to make themselves seen another
mujeres para hac hacerse ver ellos otra
user told him to dare to do
usuaria le decía que se atreva a hacer
something to harm you more than what he has already
algo para perjudicarte más de lo que ya
done so that he knows the true
ha hecho para que conozca la verdadera
cause of our 8m march if they
causa de nuestra marcha del 8m si se
mess with one they mess with all what a
meten con una se meten con todas qué
terrible feeling bad for both
terrible sentimiento mal de las dos
parties I mean This is an ex of Wherever
partes o sea Esta es una ex de Wherever
but about what suddenly came out
pero a cuento de qué de repente ha salió
with fact this is how the guys and people
con hecho así de son los weys y personas
who were sharing their
que estaban compartiendo sus
experiences are my ex recorded our
experiencias mi ex grababa nuestras
calls dis that to show them to his
llamadas dis que para mostrárselos a su
psychologist This brought me several flashbacks I am
psicóloga Esto me trajo varios flashback
grateful to have freed myself And to have
agradezco haberme liberado Y haber
gotten out of there and some pretty strong things
salido de ahí y cosas bastante fuertes
that you are seeing in the same way He
que ustedes están viendo de igual manera
already uploaded this live to YouTube titled
Ya subió este directo a YouTube titulado
reading his questions a video that lasts
leyendo sus preguntas un video que dura
a little over an hour and here I noticed
un poco más de una hora y acá noté
some parts that were more frequented or
algunas partes que más se frecuentaban o
asked for example transmitted
le preguntaban por ejemplo transmitido
transmitted the latan that says
transmitido el latan que pone
transmitted after a live instead
transmitido después de un directo en vez
of broadcast the latan says that when
de emitido el latan pone eso cuando
a live ends or  that comes out here below
termina un directo o sale eso aquí abajo
broadcasted or rather here in Spain Oh,
transmitido o sea aquí en España Ay es
candres doesn't have live shows here in
que candres no tiene directos aquí en
Spain it tells you Look, let's go to the Channel Look, it's broadcast you
España te pone Mira vamos al Canal Mira
see uncle sh Look, it's broadcasted
emitido lo veis al tío sh Mira emitido
2 hours ago Or premiered if it has been a
hace 2 horas O estrenado si ha sido un
premiere it tells you it's premiered See if
estreno te pone estrenado Mira a ver si
there's a premiere
hay algún estreno
you don't have any premiere Look, it's broadcast you
tu no hay ningún estreno Mira emitido lo
see it broadcasted but the first one
ves emitido transmitido pero la primera
totally overc elans since
de ellas sobrec totalmente elans ya que
many people are waiting for her to
muchas personas están esperando que ella
open this blue platform How do you
abra esta plataforma de color azul Cómo
say I'm not going to release an I don't understand
se dice no voy a sacar un no entiendo
why they think I'm going to release an ol that
por qué piensan que voy a sacar un ol
would be cool
estaría cool
Uh only fan only fanatics the wever
Uh only fan only fanáticos el wever
managed all her channels and now
administraba todos sus canales y ahora
that they separated he didn't return her
que se separaron no le devolvió ni sus
channels or the money those
canales ni el dinero que generaron esos
videos generated Ah the Wherever but it's the
vídeos Ah el Wherever pero es el
Wherever tomorrow that people are talking about not about
Wherever tomorrow del que se habla no de
Gabo Montiel not about this turkey who told me
Gabo Montiel no de este pavo que me dijo
in a tweet in 2018 here one that never
en un tweet en 2018 acá uno que nunca
Claro because this was I think it's that I don't
Claro porque esto fue creo que es que no
know what I put because this account was the
sé que le puse porque esta cuenta era la
other one the author of the post deleted it says I did
otra el autor del post lo eliminó dice
n't delete it they deleted my account
no lo eliminé me eliminaron la cuenta
well they didn't delete my account it's
bueno no me eliminaron la cuenta es
true the  I deleted the account,
verdad la eliminé yo la cuenta la cuenta
I deleted the account to recover this name,
la eliminé yo para recuperar este nombre
this username, uh, I mean, the
este nombre de usuario eh o sea la
account was suspended for 5 years, it
cuenta me la suspendieron durante 5 años
was suspended and this year I recovered it, I
estuvo suspendida y este año la recuperé
stole the username, I recovered it and I
robé el nombre de usuario lo recuperé y
deleted it but it was a tweet
y la eliminé pero fue un tweet
basically if I'm not mistaken it was because
básicamente si no me equivoco era porque
the Wherever was released on the
el Wherever lo sacaron en el rewind de
YouTube rewind and and I said something like what the
YouTube y y puse algo así como qué [__]
[ __ ] is this man doing, he doesn't even
pinta qué [__] pinta este hombre que no
remember him, God no, and he came to
se acuerda de él ni Dios no y me vino a
answer me super angry, oh, one who has never
responder super ardido aá uno que nunca
been a trend and has never been in
ha sido tendencia y nunca ha estado de
fashion Greetings brother and best of
moda Saludos hermano y la mejor de las
luck 2018 2018 eh guerever I was
suertes 2018 2018 eh guerever fui
a trend for almost all of 2019 I was a trend for almost all of 2020 I was a trend in Spain for almost all of 2021 well no, no, I won't tell you the whole of 2021 eh but pure facts pure facts at this
pero puros factos puros factos en este
moment it was pure facts Yes yes yes of course
momento era puros factos Sí sí sí claro
at that time it had never been but I
en ese momento nunca lo había sido pero
was very in fashion I was very fashionable  He's gone, huh He's
estuve muy de moda estuve muy de moda ya
gone, yeah, yeah, yeah, people in
se fue eh Ya se fue ya ya ya la gente en
2020, not in 2019, I was in the, let's go, in the
2020 no en 2019 estuve en el vamos en el
pic of the gossip of youtubers in 2020,
pic del salseo de youtubers en el 2020
I would say also between 2020 and 2021 and
Yo diría que también entre 2020 y 2021 y
then in 2021 it was the year of the
luego en 2021 fue el año de la
brutal gentlemen, I would say in
señoreros brutal Yo diría que en el
2021, not in 2022, it was Johnny deb, I
2021 no en el 2022 fue lo de Johnny deb
mean,
o sea
I'm always in fashion, I'm always in fashion, you have
estoy de moda siempre estoy de moda
n't followed me yet on
siempre no me habéis seguido ya en
Instagram, all of you who are here
instagram todos los que estáis aquí me
have followed me yet on Instagram, follow me because
habéis seguido ya en instagram seguidme
last night I uploaded some photos, no, last night I
que anoche subí unas fotillos no anoche
uploaded some pretty good photos, no. Let's see, look, look, look, look, look, my
subí unas fotillos bastante buenas no A
goodness, what does my place say that it's talking to me? Well, there's nothing, there's nothing,
madre mía Qué dice mi luar que me está
places, King, there's nothing, places, King, Javi, did
lugares Rey no hay nada lugares Rey Javi
you fight with Keiko or not? Who is Keiko,
peleaste con keiko o no Quién es keiko
is Lore, A Like? How is Lore, there's
está Lore A Like Cómo que está Lore hay
like because she is, Lores is, Lores is
like porque está lores está lores hay
like? But how is she, but come on  let's see,
like Pero cómo que está pero vamos a ver
don't give me a like if I'm here simply
no me dais Like si estoy yo simplemente
because I just came from the barber's I
porque est yo recién sido de la barbería
mean, what followers are these, what
O sea qué seguidores son estos qué
followers are those? This was yesterday yesterday there was a
seguidores son esos Esto fue ayer ayer
getaway yesterday there was a getaway without
hubo escapadita ayer hubo escapadita sin
kids, quiet massage, dinner Look,
niños tranquilito masaje cenita Mira
Thai place, dinner, cinema, then after
paaje tailandés cenita cine luego que
seeing a really shitty movie, eh,
vio una putísima [__] de película eh
really shitty movie, I don't
putísima [__] de película no me
remember the name of the tarot, I think it was
acuerdo cómo se llama el tarot creo que
called, and I would get a lot of money
se llamaba u le sacaría bastante
from her. I've seen that Careli is all over the place and she suddenly gets a craving, I mean, But why? Of course, there are some Lifans involved who want to open up, of course, this is a bit of a promo, no, this is a bit of an Olifan joke. No, no, no, there were
un poco bromo de olifan no no no no aquí
also those who recriminated her.
también habían quienes le recriminaba
But you said that Wherever's family
Pero tú dijiste que la familia de
was covering for him, that his
Wherever lo estaba encubriendo que sus
brothers knew about the infidelity, she
hermanos sabían de la infidelidad ella
says, at no point did I mention the
dice en ningún momento yo mencioné a la
family, here people are taking
familia acá las personas están sacando
things out of context Why do you think
las cosas de contexto Por qué piensas
his family? Yes, they knew, I never said that,
que su familia Sí lo sabía yo nunca dije
in any video I said that, oh, they
eso en ningún video dije eso oes eso lo
took that out of context, I never said, I said, there were
sacaron de contexto yo nunca dije dije
people who  they knew but I
había personas que lo sabían pero yo
never said his family another user
nunca dije que su familia otro usuario
also asked her aren't you afraid that
también le preguntó no tienes miedo de
he or his family will sue you for
que él o su familia Te demanden por
defamation long story short She says
difamación resumidas cuentas Ella dice
I have never said a name and at no
yo nunca he dicho un nombre y en ningún
time have I mentioned his family it should be
momento he mencionado a su familia cabe
noted that the crime of I have never said
recalcar que el delito de nunca he dicho
a name Jai against keiko they should already debate
un nombre Jai contra keiko ya debatan
but what are you talking about Who is
pero de qué me estáis hablando Quién es
that defamation is no longer in Mexico but
ese difamación ya no está en México pero
let's listen a little more to the explanation
escuchemos un poco más la explicación
that Fernanda gives but one I have never said
que Fernanda da pero una nunca he dicho
anyone's name I have a lot of sex Oh yeah what
el nombre de nadie tengo mucho sex Ay sí
no but I have never said
qué no pero nunca he dicho el nombre de
anyone's name And now this last and one of the
nadie Y ahora esta última y de las más
strongest the subject of her social networks
fuertes el tema de sus redes sociales
here she confesses to us that she has had
aquí ella nos confiesa ha tenido
problems literally in all
problemas literal en todas las redes
social networks apparently they are
sociales al parecer les están
restricting their content on tiktok and they
restringiendo Su contenido en tiktok y
are placing them for
se los están colocando para menores de
minors or there have perhaps been attempts or
edad o ha tenido quizás intentos o de
hacking or what is also known as
hackeo o lo que se conoce también como
Shadow One as if there is something that
Shadow One como que existe algo que le
is harming her in terms of reach and
está perjudicando en cuanto al alcance y
she tells us we already know that if something were to
ella nos dice ya sabemos que si algo
happen to my networks who is it
llegase a pasarle a mis redes de quién
about they are trying to
se trata me están este tratando de
take down my live no  I know why and
tumbar mis en vivos no sé por qué y
when I start on tiktok then they
cuando en tiktok empiezo luego luego
start putting age restrictions on me and
empiezan a ponerme restricción de edad y
what not and what Whatever says here they put in
que no y qué dice Whatever aquí ponen en
the Whatever minia is that we had a topic
la minia Whatever es que teníamos tema
about this we had topics about this and
sobre esto teníamos temas sobre esto y
in the end I didn't deal with it the other day we had we
al final no lo traté el otro día
had context about
teníamos tenemos teníamos contexto sobre
this and in the end I didn't deal with it the other day
esto y al final no lo traté el otro día
and now I don't remember what in which
y ahora no me acuerdo En qué en qué
live it was but it was a topic that was kind of
directo era pero fue un tema que como
left behind and maybe there we would
que se nos quedó atrás y a lo mejor ahí
have more context No if I
tendríamos más contexto No si lo
found it it could be This look wever
encontrase podría ser Este mira wever
accused of infidelity by his ex and his
acusado de infidelidad por su ex y su
current girlfriend deny the ex let's see click
actual novia desmienta la ex a ver click
summary with everything updated including
resumen con todo actualizado incluyendo
the thread the current girlfriend's response
el hilo la respuesta actual de la novia
this suddenly they started to make me feel very
este de repente me empezaron a poner muy
bad on social networks and I started to get
mal las redes sociales y me empezó a dar
very anxious and all that And I think I had already
mucha ansiedad y todo eso Y creo que ya
told you Then my therapist
les había contado Entonces mi terapeuta
and so they told me that let's see let's
y así me dijeron de que a ver vamos a
do an exercise don't go checking
hacer un ejercicio no te metas a revisar
comments sometimes don't go
comentarios a veces no te metas a
checking how many followers you have don't
revisar Cuántos seguidores tienes no te
go checking how many followers does such and
metas a revisar Cuántos seguidores tiene
such have And so I really lived in
tal tal tal Y así Yo la neta vivía en
an alternate reality I thought that the
una realidad alterna Yo pensaba que la
person I was with  she was super cute
persona con la que estaba era superlinda
and well gey when you realize that in the
y pues gey cuando te das cuenta que al
end she had a double life and that she wasn't
final tenía una doble vida y que no era
who you thought I'm missing a lot of context for
quien pensabas me falta mucho contexo de
this story you have to help me
esta historia me tenéis que ayudar
how long have wever been with
cuánto tiempo se ha llevado wever con
this girl and when has it been very difficult it
esta chica y cuándo ha sido muy difícil
's like understanding why I don't
es como entender el por qué no lo
need it to know clearly place myself in uh
necesito para saber claro situarme en eh
how much alluded to can be given clo she
cuánto de aludido se puede dar clo ella
is saying no no her I have not mentioned
está diciendo no no la no he mencionado
any ex I have had many exes I mean it's been
a ningún ex he tenido muchos ex o sea ha
6 years I never realized I mean
estado 6 años nunca me di cuenta o sea
that has been very difficult for me because
eso ha sido muy difícil para mí porque
you guys tell me and you didn't realize no no I didn't
ustedes me dicen y no te dabas cuenta no
realize really 7 years I
no no me daba cuenta de verdad 7 años o
mean 7 years so very complicated that she does
sea 7 años entonces muy complicado que
n't take it as a hint Whatever no Even though she does
no se de por aludido Whatever no Por más
n't say her name I didn't realize it's that
que no diga su nombre no me daba cuenta
why if it was always told to you that she did
es que por qué si siempre se te dijo que
n't want to get married no no no let's see
no se quería casar no no no a ver a mí
I love it because people seem to
me encanta porque como que la gente se
forget there was even a video
le olvida había hasta hicimos un video
of that that according to that we loved him And
de eso de que según lo queríamos Y
how long has it been since they broke up to me it was
cuánto hace que lo han dejado a mí se me
told according to that he didn't want children and blah blah blah
dijo según que no se quería hijos y bla
because of mom and I Okay  I
bla bla que porque por mamá y yo Okay lo
accepted one makes decisions also
acepté uno toma decisiones también
based on the couple and so no
basadas en en la pareja y y así no
then this I always clarified that I did
entonces este yo siempre aclaré que yo
want to get married so to me it
sí me quería casar entonces a mí luego
seems very strange that people say
se me hace muy extraño que la gente diga
no but it's why Why yes if
de que no pero es que por qué Por qué si
you knew that he didn't want to get married let's see
si tú sabías que no se quería casar a
No they told me something else to me it was
ver No a mí se me decía otra cosa a mí
half a year ago they broke up more or
se me hace medio año lo dejaron más o
less something totally different you know I
menos otra cosa totalmente diferente
found out that he was already with
saben yo me enteré que estaba ya con
someone else when we broke up and that was what I'm
alguien más cuando cortamos y eso fue lo
telling you that shocked me or rather
que lo que les digo me impactó o sea el
realizing that I've been
darme cuenta que ya he llevado más de do
with the person who is there for more than two and a half years it was
años y medio con la persona que está fue
like gu you didn't have the balls to tell me I
como gu no tuviste los huevos de decirme
don't want to be with you I want to be with
no quiero estar contigo quiero estar con
someone else you know I mean I don't know or rather how
alguien más sabes o sea no sé o sea lo
little man people are sometimes
poco hombre que a veces son las personas
not keeping their word not having the balls
el no tener palabra el no tener huevos
not having uh commitment not being
el no tener eh compromiso el no ser
firm when making a decision you know I lived
firmes ante una decisión sabes yo vivía
in an alternate reality I
en una realidad alterna yo pensaba
literally thought that I was going to get married that my life
literal que me iba a casar que mi vida
was super happy that they were super
era superfeliz que estaban super
in love with me Well that we
enamoradísimos de mí Pues de que
broke up because when the
terminamos porque ya cuando se hace el
announcement was made I started getting messages
anuncio me empiezan a llegar mensajes a
me and then someone also made a
mí y después alguien también hizo un
Twitter thread and they sent me that
hilo de Twitter y me mandaban mucho ese
Twitter thread a lot and that's where I
hilo de Twitter y ahí fue donde yo
discovered a lot of things a lot of videos and the
descubrí muchas cosas muchos videos y lo
most painful thing was also realizing
más doloroso también fue darme cuenta
that I was never respected you know I mean it was
que nunca se me respetó saben o sea que
n't these two years Now the
no fueron estos estos dos años Ahora la
other girl lives in the house where she
otra chica vive en la casa donde ella
lived with him and half or more of those who
vivía con él y medio o más de los que me
cheated on me he always cheated on me I mean There were always there were
engañó siempre me engañó o sea Siempre
people uh third parties you don't
hubo hubo hubo personas eh terceras no
realize that you take people
te das cuenta que te llevas a la gente
between your legs that that I mean because
entre las patas que que o sea porque
for me it was the shock I mean imagine that
para mí fue el shock o sea imagínense de
apart it's how I tell you ending
que aparte es como les digo terminar con
a relationship and a relationship so long in the
una relación y una relación tan larga al
end I lost Well a partner a
final perdí Pues a una pareja a una
person that I thought was my friend
persona que yo creía que era mi amiga
a person with whom I slept that in the
una persona con la que dormía que al
end that was also a shock the Don't
final eso también fue un shock el No
[ __ ] with me I was with a person so many years
[__] estuve con una persona tantos años
of my life and I never knew who he
de mi vida y nunca supe quién era
really was don't [ __ ] with I mean don't [ __ ] with That
realmente no [__] O sea no [__] Eso sí
is a mega shock it's like How with whom I
es un mega shock es como Cómo con quién
was what happened Why I never
estuve qué pasó Por qué nunca me di
realized that now in the process that I am going through
cuenta que ahora en el proceso que voy
is forgiving myself you know why  I
es el perdonarme a mí saben porque me
blamed him a lot how did you not realize
culpaba mucho el como no te diste cuenta
eh because you did not see these attitudes
eh porque estas actitudes no las viste
because obviously after it happens, well, you
porque obviamente después de que pasa
start to open your eyes and
pues ya empiezas a abrir los ojos y a
notice certain attitudes No, apart from being a
notar ciertas actitudes No aparte
hypocrite Oh, no, that's the worst thing
hipócrita Ay no es eso es lo peor que
you guys say Oh, did you realize, like at
ustedes dicen ay te diste cuenta como
first he wanted to paint her as if oh, you
que primero quiso pintarla de que ay me
were unfaithful to me Poor me Don't [ __ ] with me and I
fueron infiel Pobrecito de mí No [__] y
started to make audios of Tito Guillo
empezaba a hacer audios de Tito guillo
geey but I didn't want to hold her hands
geey pero pues no quería la las manos
before he could get out Freed and for nobody,
antes para él salir Librado y que nadie
nobody, nobody to say No, he's been in
nadie nadie dijera No él ya tiene con
that relationship for almost 3 years, no
esa relación desde hace casi 3 años no
Fernanda was like that, look at life Oh,
Fernanda andaba así miren por la vida Ay
Noah, ugly, how ugly, what do you think, she cheated on
no Noé feo qué feo ustedes qué pensáis
him or didn't tell him
que le puso los cuernos o que no le dijo
that she wanted an open relationship? I think what
que quería una relación abierta yo creo
she's saying is true, no,
que lo que cuenta Ella es verdad no
then, No, that's a shock, babies
entonces u No eso eso es un shock bebés
Because they had broken up and you found
Porque habían terminado y todo te
out about everything, then for other things, what
enteraste desp por otras cosas lo que
she's saying is true, I think, eh,
cuenta Ella es verdad lo puede pienso eh
like, a little bit of the reason why I
como quea un poco el motivo del por qué
'm telling it now, okay And there
lo estoy contando ahora vale Y ahí
I think it could be, let's see if she's
pienso que puede ser a ver si si está
considering the  possibility of an Olly fan
barajando la posibilidad de un Olly fan
because she's promoting
pues está promocionándose
Whatever wasn't very well known anymore no
Whatever ya no estaba muy conocido no
but I imagine that for her audience this
pero me imagino que para su público esta
girl was well known no sometimes
chica sí era conocida no a veces también
people also think that don't [ __ ] with Hania Balades
la gente cree que no [__] hania balades
Hania Balades thanks for these 20
hania balades gracias por estos 20
so this also a lot of
entonces este también pasaron muchas
things happened that I'll tell you about later that little by
cosas que ya les iré contando que poco a
little Wever's brother was also
poco el hermano de wever también le fue
unfaithful to his wife that's how they are but
infiel a su esposa así son ellos pero
well I don't know I think my goodness what a
pues no sé creo que madre mía menuda
humiliation that that Wever puts it on you
humillación que el wever ese te ponga lo
Eh This has been like the most
cueno Eh Esto ha sido como que lo más
bastard like the most bastard what a
cabrón como que lo más cabrón menuda
humiliation that anyone puts it on you
humillación que te lo ponga cualquiera
eh but that they put it on you that
eh pero que te lo ponga que te lo ponga
Wherever puts it on you more difficult I mean like it's
Wherever más difícil o sea como que ha
been a process a duel and the most
sido un proceso un duelo y lo más
difficult thing I think has been what happened with my
difícil creo que sí ha sido lo de mis
dogs I mean in the end because I understood
perros o sea ya al final porque entendí
that I said gey who I was
que yo dije gey de quién estuve
in love with I don't know you know I never knew
enamorada no sé sabes Nunca supe de
who I was in love with eh I never
quién estuve enamorada eh nunca conocí
really knew the person I mean imagine
realmente a la persona O sea imagínate
that you live almost 7 years of your life with
que vives casi 7 años de tu vida con
someone and then you find out that
alguien y que después te enteres que
always  did he see your face that I was leading a
siempre te vio la cara que llevaba una
literal double life, I mean gey What No
una doble vida literal o sea gey What No
way, I don't even know who to cry to, I don't
[__] no sé ni a quién llorarle no sé
know, you know, but everything hurts, all the bad things he
sabes pero me duele todo todo lo malo
did to me, making fun of me,
que me hizo porque el burlarse de mí el
like they put it on you with orlock Yeah
como que te lo pongan con orlock Sí
sure clo but what's the Ever telling you dude
claro clo pero que te cue el Ever tío
What a thing to see my face Javi
Qué cosita el verme la cara Javi dato
curious fact she is very feminist and very good
curioso ella es muy feminista y muy
friends with Ari Gameplay no, I'm not going to
amiga de Ari Gameplay no no voy a
prejudge someone by who their
prejuzgar a alguien por quien sea su
friend is or if they are a feminist or not I mean,
amiga o por si es feminista o no O sea
sincerely, I'm listening to the
sinceramente estoy escuchando la
story and from the information that you're
historia y y por los datos que me estáis
giving me the truth is that no, no, I don't see
dando la verdad es que no no no le veo
the reason why Why would she make it up,
el motivo de por qu lo Por qué se lo
right? But anyway, let's
inventaría no Pero bueno vamos a
also hear the other version now.
escuchar también la otra versión ahora
Thanks, I think also realizing
Gracias creo que también el darme cuenta
that for more than 2 and a half years she
que que yo durante más de 2 años y medio
was in another relationship. That was
me estuvo en otra relación Eso fue
too much for me, you know that, that for more
demasiado para mí saben eso eso que más
than 2 and a half years she was in another uh
de 2 años y medio estuvo otra eh
relationship, well let's see, really, if I could,
relación bueno a ver en verdad si podría
if it's that type of feminism. Yes, I could
si es ese tipo de feminismo Sí podría
prejudge a little, no, there are some that
prejuzgar un poco no hay algunas que
tend to be very liars, no  and they
suelen ser muy mentirosas no y se
make up stories and stuff no, that I think
inventan historias y demás no eso creo
was the most shocking thing for me
que fue lo más choque an para mí cara
after I realized that her
después de que me di cuenta que que su
current relationship was with Yuya since don't
relación actual la tenía desde que no se
forget that when she broke up with Yuya she did
olvide que cuando cortó con Yuya hizo
a lot to make her look bad too
mucho hacerla quedar mal también madre
my goodness I'm still in shock that the Werever was
mía yo todavía alucino de que el Werever
with Yuya eh I don't know if it's that I do
haya estado con Yuya eh No sé si es que
n't know the reasons it's that I wasn't
no sé los motivo es que ahí ya no estaba
that into YouTube yet when I
yo tan en YouTube todavía yo ya cuando
arrived it was almost the end when
llegué casi que fue el final en el que
they went viral you know we
ellos fueran virales sabes algún vídeo
managed to release some videos of Yuya and stuff but no it
llegamos a sacar de Yuya y demás pero no
wasn't there for long when I
no estuvo mucho tiempo cuando ya yo
arrived you know and especially the Werever
llegué sabes y sobre todo el Werever
but the wever with Yuya man I mean and I don't care
pero el wever con Yuya tío o sea y me da
eh I mean I'm not messing with
igual eh o sea no me estoy metiendo con
anyone's physique no I'm not
el físico de nadie no no lo estoy
insulting him but objectively
insultando pero objetivamente
objectively I mean Yuya is a
objetivamente o sea Yuya es una
beauty okay Okay now I see it place I mean she's
preciosidad vale Okay ahora lo veo lugar
really cute she's really cute okay And
o sea es monísima es monísima vale Y
Wherever is wherever How come yya is just
Wherever es wherever Cómo que yya es del
average super
montón super
cute well I'm really glad that you
mona bien Me da mucho gusto que hayan
came to this meeting that was only
venido a esta reunión que fue solamente
for dad I imagine that maybe he would
para padre yo me imagino que a lo mejor
become famous and when he becomes  famous because he
se haría famoso y al hacerse famoso pues
would have cancer to those types of women
tendría al cáncer a ese tipo de mujeres
and then he's not faithful and doesn't know how to
y luego pues no es fiel y no sabe
say no or appreciate what he has
decirle que no ni apreciar lo que tenga
or things like that. I've been doing it for almost three
o cosas por el estilo Yo hace casi TR
years or more, I don't know, it usually happens a lot, eh,
años o más no sé suele pasar mucho eh
with guys when they become famous, eh, I
con los tíos cuando se hacen famosos eh
understood, I understood, you know, I understood, I found out
entendí entendí sabes entendí me enteré
that he had a relationship for more than two
de que tenía una relación por más de dos
years when I found out everything, you don't know
años cuando yo me enteré todo no saben
how I threw up. I mean, I was in shock, I
cómo vomitaba O sea estaba en shock o
mean, really. Imagine that you're in
sea de verdad Imagínate que tú estás en
your normal house, you just broke up with
tu casa normal tú acabas de terminar con
your ex, it hurts because it hurts, it hurts,
tu ex te duele porque te duele te duele
but you say, geey, let's go, we're
pero dices geey ter amos bien estamos
sharing the dogs, everything is
compartiendo a los perritos todo está
flowing, super cool. Okay, I had never
fluyendo super chido Okay yo nunca había
met up with, I had never thought about
quedado con de nunca había pensado
meeting up with my ex as a friend and in that, you're in
quedar con mi ex de amiga y en eso estás
your house sitting down, they tag you and
en tu casa sentada te etiquetan y te
tag you and it's a lot, you open the link. There it
etiquetan y es mucho abres el link ahí
tells us about the thread that Fernanda
nos habla del hilo que Fernanda nos
tells us that when she went to get her things for
cuenta que cuando fue por sus cosas por
some things that she had in the house
unas cosas que ella tenía en la casa
where she lived, where she lived with. Let's see,
donde convivía donde vivía con a ver
guys, Javi, censor, you're going to respond
chicos Javi censurador vas a responderle
to the angry writer, let's see, but that would be
al escritor ardido a ver pero eso sería
telesalseo I'll see I don't know the truth is
telesalseo Ya veré No lo sé la verdad es
why do I want another one why do I want another one
que para qué quiero otro para qué quiero
hooked already I have too many
otro enganchado ya Tengo demasiada gente
sick people hooked on my arm well
malita enganchada en mi brazo bueno en
anyway that's what's left no it won't be like that
fin es lo que queda no no quedará eso
forever I don't know the same tomorrow we'll
toda la vida no sé lo mismo mañana ya lo
see Tomorrow I have a
vemos Es que mañana tengo un directo
nice live show tomorrow at 10 there's a nice live show
guapo mañana a las 10 hay un directo
with trium with l for loves julan
guapo con trium con l de amores julan
is so beautiful the baby turned out
está tan hermosa que la guagua le salió
gorgeous I don't know what the baby is What is
preciosa no sé qué es la guagua Qué es
the baby another bad one for the collection
la guagua otro malito para la colección
get ready Javi Ugh they sent me some tw's
prepárate Javi Uf me mandaron algunos tw
that he's putting on a show and brutal eh Ah
que está poniendo el pavo y brutal eh Ah
The sensor sensor baby imagine the nug
El bebé sensor sensor imagínate a la nug
with Yuya clar with juna clar
con Yuya clar con juna clar hostias
literal [ __ ] eh bu let's see the anug It's that the
literal eh bu a ver el anug Es que la
nug is worse not than the Wherever no [ __ ]
nug es peor no que el Wherever no [__]
Well I don't know they're different types of ugliness
Pues no lo sé son tipos de fealdades
because the n Imagine
diferentes porque es que la n Imagínate
the moror with cristinini not even the millor is
al moror con cristinini ni el millor es
as ugly as wever nor cristinini is
tan tan feo como wever ni cristinini es
as pretty as juna let's see well
tan tan guapa como juna a ver bueno
cristinini pretty  also yes it is uglier
cristinini guapita también sí es más feo
to anug Uf It's that the anug is not only
a anug Uf Es que la anug ya no solamente
the ugly ones It's that you know it's an accumulation of
los feos Es que sabes es un cúmulo de
things it's like the chul with est yuki
cosas es como el chul con est yuki
[ __ ] [ __ ] to see went up and
cabrones cabrones de ver subió y se
found lingerie lingerie that was not
encontró lencería lencería que no era de
hers so that was where she began to
ella así que fue ahí donde empezó a
connect the dots and realized that
conectar los puntos y se dio cuenta que
he already had another partner and sometimes I
él ya tenía otra pareja y yo a veces
needed to go get my things and
necesitaba ir por por mis cosas y no se
I was not allowed to enter where I had
me permitía entrar a donde yo había
lived to where supposedly had been
vivido a donde supuestamente había sido
my house, I mean I could not go whenever I
mi casa o sea yo no podía ir cuando yo
wanted to pick up my shoes my clothes, I
quisiera a recoger mis zapatos mi ropa o
mean I had to ask permission you know so
sea tenía que pedir permiso sab entonces
the first time I go and they had
la primera vez que voy y habían dejado
obviously left lingerie that was not
así obviamente una lencería que no era
mine and Well apart from that very courteous
mía y Bueno aparte sí de que muy cortero
what he tells us is that all the money
lo que nos Comenta es que todo el dinero
that was generated both in his own channel
que se generaba tanto en su canal propio
and in the one they had as a couple, all the
como en el que tenían en pareja todo el
money fell into the Wherever card
dinero caía en la tarjeta de Wherever
so she did not know how much money she
por lo que ella no sabía cuánto dinero
was generating there I am not saying
estaba generando ahí no estoy diciendo
anything that I cannot prove, did she
nada que yo no pueda demostrar alguna
ever stop paying you for something from your channel
vez te dejó de pagar algo de tu canal
Well look, I never got the money and I
Pues mira a mí nunca me cayó el dinero y
never knew how much I earned in
nunca supe en sí cuánto ganaba en
general always  I had 30%
general siempre a mí se me quitó el 30%
of
de todo
everything taken from my YouTube channel's campaigns
de todo de campañas de mi canal de
on my Facebook page, using a lot of
YouTube de mi Facebook utizando mucho
people who are not supporting
las personas que no están apoyando a
Fernanda Blas who are supporting a lot,
Fernanda Blas que están apoyando aorro
which are many, they are. Well, look, it's
que son muchas es que están Pues mira es
a good deal, eh. When you get a
un buen trato eh Cuando te eches una
girlfriend who's going to gain fame at your expense,
novia que vaya a ganar fama a cosa tuya
charging her 30% of everything isn't bad,
cobrarle el 30% de todo no está mal
mother of God. eh, commenting that Fernanda would
madre de Dios eh comentando que Fernanda
not have been grateful to Wherever
no habría sido agradecida con Wherever
because if it hadn't been for, I insist,
ya que si no hubiera sido por insisto
Wherever is one of those sexist, like,
Wherever es de esos machistas como peso
featherweight, that vibe, she wouldn't have been
pluma esa onda ella no hubiera sido
famous, that many people say, oh
famosa de que muchas personas dicen ay
well, I should be grateful. Of course I
pues debería de estar agradecida Claro
thanked him. But how
que le que le agradecí Pero cuánto
long, how long if he?
tiempo cuánto tiempo si él De todas
Anyway, he earned 30% from me, well, he
formas ganaba de mí el 30% pues él se
kept 30% of the profits.
quedaba con el 30% de las ganancias Por
Which is why she feels that this
lo cual ella siente que es ese ese
gratitude was already fulfilled because
agradecimiento ya estaba cumplido porque
he also kept part of
él también se quedaba con parte de las
Fernanda's own profits for making her
ganancias de la propia Fernanda por
famous, nobody told me what to do.
haberla hecho famosa nadie me manvo c o
Since she comments that she has always
no Ya que ella comenta que ella siempre
had very good views.  Well, she has
ha tenido muy buenas vistas pues tiene
millions of views, she's not someone who
millones de visitas no es alguien como
has 100,000 subscribers or anything like
que tenga 100,000 suscriptores ni nada
that, but she has millions of
por así sino que ella tiene millones de
followers on social media and she doesn't
seguidores en redes sociales y que no lo
do it for views because in general her
hace por vistas porque en general a sus
videos are doing very well. They
videos le va muy bien Le vuelven a
ask her again if she's going. Damn, but she had a
preguntar si va [__] pero tenía un un
ton of views. This girl, I don't know
montonazo de visita yo Esta tía no sé
who she is, but if she had 2 million,
quién es [__] pero si tenía 2 millones
2 million views on average on
de 2 millones de visitas de media en
each video, I'm [ __ ] myself and I
cada vídeo me cago en la [__] y os
'm telling you, I'm asking you
estoy diciendo os estoy preguntando que
if she was known, yeah, if people knew
si era conocid yaa que si sabía la gente
who she was and I'm [ __ ] myself. Well, it's
Quién era y me cago un d Pues sí que se
known who she is, in terms of followers on
sabe quién es no de seguidores en redes
social media and she doesn't do it for views
sociales y que no lo hace por vistas
because in general her videos are doing
porque en general a suos videos le va
very well. They ask her again if she's
muy bien Le vuelven a preguntar si va a
going with a certain Fredo. And it seems that Fernanda
ir con un tal fredo Y se ve que Fernanda
Blas isn't convinced yet, she says,
Blas no está convencida aún ella dice
well, I'm telling you here because they
pues lo estoy contando acá porque
want me to go with Fredo. The thread says,
quieren que vaya con fredo el hilo dice
like, already deleted. Obviously, the thread with
así ya borrado Obviamente el hilo con
those parts carried or deleted says, I'm opening a
esas partes portadas o borradas dice
thread like Gabriel Montiel Wherever
abro hilo como Gabriel Montiel Wherever
is an unfaithful narcissist and  he likes to
es un narcisista infiel y le gusta
play the victim this thread was made on
hacerse la víctima este hilo se hizo con
January 4th of this year at
fecha de 4 de enero del presente año a
12:55 in the morning then he says Don't you find it
las 12:55 de la madrugada luego dice No
strange that Gabriel Always
se les hace extraño que Gabriel Siempre
ends up playing the victim with his
se termine haciendo la víctima con sus
exes after he cheats on them
exes después de que les pone el cuerno
when in reality he is the unfaithful one he attaches
cuando en realidad es el infiel adjunta
evidence and people are saying here
pruebas y la gente está diciendo por acá
and the thread Where is the thread because I
y el hilo Dónde está el hilo porque les
tell you that eh it lasted a short time someone
digo que eh duró poco tiempo alguien
reported this thread and
reportó este hilo y se dieron de baja
this evidence was removed however I have a
estas pruebas sin embargo yo tengo una
screenshot not with the detailed screenshots I am
captura no con Las capturas a detalle
going to put this on screen of what
este lo voy a poner en pantalla de lo
the thread was so that you have an
que era el hilo para que tú tengas una
idea of what was being shown in
idea de lo que se estaba mostrando en
said publication Oh well and well He is
dicha publicación Ah bueno y bueno Él se
also seen in the video with his
ve en el video también con con su pareja
current partner And obviously that person
actual Y pues obviamente esa persona
has tattoos and well it is from two years ago
tiene tatuada y pues es de hace dos años
and something that Fernanda Blas mentioned
y tanto algo que mencionó Fernanda Blas
that surprised me a lot is that
que a mí me sorprendió muchísimo es que
she mentions that when he approaches or
ella menciona que cuando él se acerca o
rather has a photograph where you can see the
sea tiene fotografía donde se ve el
arm of this girl and by the tattoos it is
brazo de esta chica y por los tatuajes
recognized that she is the current girlfriend
se le reconoce a que es la novia actuala
to flirt with certain girls surely he
a ligar a ciertas chicas seguramente lo
saw it in the thread the truth is I do not know well
vio en el hilo la verdad no sé bien De
Where did he see that according to this the girls
dónde vio eso según esto las chicas
were saying Hey but why do you want to
decían Oye pero pues por qué quieres
hit on me if you have a girlfriend and that
ligarme a mí si tú tienes novia y que el
Whatever responded Ah it doesn't count anymore what
Whatever respondía Ah ya no cuenta qué
how he answered when they told him but
cómo contestaba cuando le decían pero
you have a girlfriend but it doesn't count but it's not worth it
tienes novia pero no cuenta pero no vale
mentions that in those tests in that thread you could
menciona que en esas pruebas de ese hilo
see his current partner who has been with
se veía a su actual pareja que lleva con
her according to Fernanda for 2 and a half years and
ella según Fernanda 2 años y medio y
dude he's with her and well she has tattoos
güey está él con ella y pues ella está
and you can see the tattoos and
tatuada y se le ven los tatuajes y
obviously they are the same and there the
obviamente son los mismos y ahí las
dates are the ones that's why I
fechas son las que por eso yo me di
realized and the new gossip Fernanda
cuenta y el chisme nuevo Fernanda nos
tells us that the lion believes that everyone is like
cuenta que el león cree que todos son de
her Why Because Whatever
su condición Por qué Porque el Whatever
According to this he was always telling her
Según esto siempre le estaba diciendo
Hey why don't you answer me if Fernanda
Oye por qué no me contestas si Fernanda
didn't answer him in 30 minutes he would tell her
no le respondía en 30 minutos le decía
where are you with who are you with as if
dónde estás con quién estás así como que
doubting her fidelity Fernanda
dudando de la fidelidad de ella Fernanda
says Well Len thinks that everything is his
dice Bueno León cre que todo es su
condition because with me it was
condición porque conmigo sí era
different because Len believes that everyone is like
diferente porque León cree que todos son
his condition I mean they asked me if
de su condición O sea a mí me pedían si
I didn't answer in an hour half an hour it
yo no contestaba en una hora media hora
was like Don't [ __ ] with me what are you doing They
era de No [__] qué estás haciendo Le
called my mom yes  I was in
marcaban a mi mamá si yo estaba en
Jalapa, so to speak, and at the end she ends up
Jalapa o sea y al final remata
telling us that when they ended their
contándonos que cuando terminaron su
relationship, Gabriel proposed having an
relación Gabriel le propuso tener una
open relationship. What when we were
relación abierta qué cuando estábamos
talking about, well, when it was going to end, it was,
hablando de pues ya cuando iba a acabar
but okay, so we can
todo fue pero bueno entonces podemos
have an open relationship, dude, it was. Well,
tener una relación abierta gey fue Bueno
now it's okay to be exclusive. If she wants to
pues ahora sí les va la exclus si quiere
have an open relationship, that she's not
tener una relación abierta que no está
satisfied, no. I mean, why do you want to
satisfecho no O sea para qué quieres
be with her? Then because you
estar con ella Entonces porque ustedes
know that Mau rg1 is an
saben que Mau rg1 es un canal de
exclusive channel, a message came from Sofia
exclusivas llegó un mensaje de Sofía
Zaval, deever's girlfriend. I said, Well, let's
zaval la novia deever dije Bueno pues a
see what happened, she writes to me: Hello,
ver qué qué habrá pasado me escribe Hola
ma, good night. I hope you're doing very well. I
ma buenas noches Espero estés muy bien
wanted to see if she can talk to you. I
Quería ver si puede hablar contigo le le
told her yes and she wrote me the
puse que sí y ella me escribió lo
following: I wasn't going to pay attention to the subject,
siguiente no iba a hacer caso del tema
but these days it exploded and the
pero en estos días explotó y los
messages I've been receiving are very
mensajes que me han llegado están muy
stupid and worrying, to the point of
sobidos y preocupantes al grado de
threatening to go out of their way and send me my
amenazarme de desvivir y enviarme Mi
address, dude, I didn't know that this
dirección güey que yo no sabía que esta
person thinks and declares that I am the
persona piensa y declara que yo soy la
person in the video that appears in a
persona del video que aparece en un hilo
Twitter thread dated more than 2 years ago and
de Twitter con fecha de más de 2 años y
that at some point you
que en algún momento tú llegaste a
shared it, look here even the same
compartirlo fíjense aquí hasta la misma
Sofia says it and at some point you
Sofía lo dice y en algún momento tú
shared it in a
llegaste a compartirlo en un video
YouTube video months ago. I approached you with
YouTube hace ya meses me acerco a ti con
evidence that said video was recorded
pruebas de que dicho video fue grabado
on September 19, 2021. There is another one from
el 19 de septiembre del 2021 ahí otra de
that same day in which you can see that it is
ese mismo día en la que se puede ver que
not me. I am attaching it and with
no soy yo te lo adjunto y con
photographs of me at that time already
fotografías de mí en ese entonces ya
completely tattooed on my left arm. I do
tatuada completamente el brazo izquierdo
not want to be involved in a
no quiero estar involucrada en una
controversy, much less in times and
polémica ni mucho menos en tiempos y
relationships that do not concern me. What
relaciones que no me competen lo que
happened when I did not meet
haya pasado cuando yo no conocí a
Gabriel is something else. Thank you very much for
Gabriel es otra cosa Muchas gracias por
the space and I hope that with your dissemination you
el espacio y ojalá con tu difusión me
can help me stop this massive harassment
puedas ayudar a que este acoso masivo
a little. She sends me a video here
pare un poco y me envía por acá un video
that we are going to put on the screen. What she
que vamos a pasar a la pantalla ella lo
is saying is that,
que está diciendo el punto es que ella
from what I understand, she has not been with Wherever
por lo que entiendo no anda con Wherever
for more than two and a half years, as is
desde hace más de do años y medio como
being commented on social networks. I do not
se está comentando en redes sociales no
know exactly how long the
sé cuánto tiempo exactamente tenga la
relationship between Sofa Zavala and Gabriel
relación entre Sofía Zavala y Gabriel
Montiel has been going on. This is what she sends me. How do you
Montiel Esto es lo que me envía Cómo se
say it? Oh well and well. He is also seen in the
dice Ah bueno y bueno Él se ve en el
video with his current partner. And
video también con con su pareja actual Y
obviously that person has a
pues obviamente esa persona tiene
tattoo and well, it is from years ago.  two years and
tatuada y pues es de hace dos años y
so on and also that is merged into the thread
tantos y también eso lo fuson en el hilo
this video that you are watching
este video que tú estás viendo me lo
she sent it to me eh also that's why I
envió ella eh también por eso yo Lo
discovered it because and here it says eh the
descubrí porque y aquí pone eh la
recording where there are some girls and there
grabación donde están unas chicas y ahí
is the Whatever tor there is elever you can
está el Whatever tor ahí está elever se
see the arm You can go pause
ve el brazo Ustedes pueden ir pausando
this Sofia what she does is cover
esta Sofía lo que hace es taparle la
this girl's face because she doesn't want to
cara a esta chica porque no quiere
expose Who these girls are and there is
exponer Quién es estas chicas y ahí está
elever okay This is the video you can see that she
elever vale Este es el vídeo se ve que
has a tattoo but you can't
tiene tatuaje pero no se pueden
differentiate the tattoos well no and here it
diferenciar los tatuajes bien no y aquí
says eh the recording where there are some girls
pone eh la grabación d están unas chicas
and there is the Whatever torro there is the
y ahí está el Whatever torro ahí está el
Whatever you can see the arm You can
Whatever se ve el brazo Ustedes pueden
go pause this Sofia what she does is
ir pausando esta Sofía lo que hace es
cover this girl's face because she doesn't
taparle la cara a esta chica porque no
want to expose Who she is I mean the girl's face
quiere exponer Quién es O sea la cara de
But how do we know it's not
la chica Pero cómo sabemos que no es
her well by the teeth too but
ella bueno por los dientes también pero
by the left arm Sofia Zavala in
por el brazo izquierdo Sofía Zavala en
2021 already had her left arm tattooed which is why
2021 ya tenía tatuado el brazo izquierdo
she is sharing
razón por la cual ella está compartiendo
this proof where you see Whatever With
esta prueba donde se ve a Whatever Con
this girl who covers the girl's eyes
esta chica que tapa los ojos de la chica
to protect her identity Because
para proteger su identidad Porque
surely they would throw a lot of hate at
seguramente le tirarían mucho hate a
this girl because from what I understand it
esta chica porque por lo que entiendo no
wasn't one but several girls But
fue una sino fueron varias chicas Pero
the point that this Sofia Zavala is making
el punto que está diciendo esta Sofía
is don't relate me to those
Zavala es a mí no me relacionen con esas
dates from more than 2 years ago
fechas de hace más de 2 años ya que
since August 7, 2021 when that
desde 7 de agosto de 2021 cuando fue esa
party was, which is the video that they are
fiesta que es el video que le están
relating to her, Conor, at that party,
relacionando a ella conor en esa fiesta
she already had her left arm tattooed
ella ya tenía el brazo izquierdo tatuado
and this girl with whom Gabriel
y esta chica con la que aparece Gabriel
Montiel appears at all times In this video
Montiel en todo momento En este video
that appears in that thread, look at this is
que sale en ese hilo fíjense esto es
information, well now it's exclusive
información pues ahora sí que exclusiva
because it is information that had been
porque es información que se había
deleted from Twitter, what I told you even
borrado de Twitter lo que les dije hasta
the teeth are different and of course, but you
los dientes son diferentes y claro pero
know what happens, look at this
es que sabes qué pasa que mira que esta
Instagram story, I don't know, but
historia de Instagram No lo sé pero las
Instagram stories are usually in but mode, they are usually the other way
historias de Instagram suelen ser en
around So the
modo peo suelen ser al revés Entonces
same, uh, the same Here we see that it is an
igual eh igual Aquí vemos que es un
arm that is seen with which
brazo el que se ve con la que aparece
Gabriel Montiel appears at all times In this
Gabriel Montiel en todo momento En este
video that appears in that Here he is looking
video que sale en ese Aquí está mirando
to the side, look at this is information,
para un lado fíjense esto es información
well now it's exclusive because it is
pues ahora sí que exclusiva porque es
information that had been deleted from
información que se había borrado de
Twitter, what I told you even the
Twitter lo que les diga hasta los
teeth are different and veneers that I
dientes son diferentes y carillas que yo
don't  I respect the other person and I did
no tengo por respeto a la otra persona y
not involve anyone else in this case, I am not
no involucré a nadie más en este caso no
showing her face. Thank you very much and I
muestro su cara Muchas gracias y aquí la
put it here that I understand that I seduce her in
puse que le entiendo que la coso en
all ways, it is not justifiable and that it is
todas formas no es justificable y que
wrong that they are threatening her, or in other words,
está mal que le estén amenazando o sea
the photo in the thread where this Sofa
la foto del hilo donde sale esta Sofía
Zavala appears in the house of Whatever where she
Zavala en la casa de Whatever donde
lived with Fernanda Blas and she is saying that it
vivía con Fernanda Blas y está diciendo
was on January 2, 2024 when she
eso fue del 2 de enero del 2024 cuando
had already broken up with Fernanda Blas.
ya había terminado con Fernanda Blas
Well, if something else comes out, we will
Bueno pues si sale algo más iremos
see. For now, it seems quite
viendo de momento me resulta bastante
short to me. Not yet the information that there
cortito No todavía la información que
is. But well, we will see.
hay Pero bueno veremos
[Music]
[Música]